{
	"Quiz1": [
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 1,
			"Question_1": "RAM stands for Random",
			"Question_2": "Memory",
			"Answer": "Access",
			"Explanation": "RAM stands for Random Access Memory"
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 2,
			"Question" : "Which is not an Access modifiers in Java? (Choose All the Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Default",
			"Choice2" : "Private",
			"Choice3" : "Sergent",
			"Answer" : [3],
			"Explanation" : "Sergent is not an access modifer in Java.  It is a rank in the military."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 3,
			"Question": "Which is not a OOP Concepty?",
			"Choice1" : "Abstraction",
			"Choice2" : "Multi-threaded",
			"Choice3" : "Encapsulation",
			"Answer": "Choice2",
			"Explanation": "Abstraction and Ecapsulation are both concepts in Object-Oriented Programming.  Multi-Threading is not."
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 4,
			"Question" : "What is the ability of an object to take on many forms called?",
			"Answer": "Polymorphism",
			"Explanation": "Polymorphism is the ability of an object to take many forms."
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 5,
			"Question_1": "The",
			"Question_2": "is the fastest sorting Algorithm",
			"Answer": "Quicksort",
			"Explanation": "Quicksort is the fastest sorting Algorithm"
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :6,
			"Question" : "What is the process where one object acquires the properties of another?",
			"Answer": "Inheritance",
			"Explanation": "Inheritance is the process where one object acquires the properties of another."
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 7,
			"Question" : "Are variables in python strongly typed?",
			"Answer" : "False",
			"Explanation" : "Variables are loosley types in python."
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :8,
			"Question" : "What is a method that has the same name as that of the class to which it belongs and as soon as a new object is created, gets invoked?",
			"Answer": "Constructor",
			"Explanation": "A constructor is a method that has the same name as that of the class to which it belongs to and gets invokes as soon as a new object is created."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num" : 9,
			"Question": "Where does RAM go?",
			"Choice1" : "On a Mountain",
			"Choice2" : "On the Road",
			"Choice3" : "Inside a computer",
			"Answer" : "Choice3",
			"Explanation" : "RAM, in this case, is a computer component."
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 10,
			"Question" : "Which are sorting algorithms? (Choose All the Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Heap",
			"Choice2" : "Radix",
			"Choice3" : "Pop",
			"Answer" : [1,2],
			"Explanation" : "There is no sorting algorithm called Pop."
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 11,
			"Question" : "What is the concept of assigning a variable of one data type to a variable of another data type?",
			"Answer": "Typecasting",
			"Explanation": "Typecasting is the concept of assigning a variable of one data type to a variable of another data type.  It is not possible for the boolean data type, however."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 12,
			"Question": "What is a Microprocessor?",
			"Choice1" : "A small machine to shred cheese",
			"Choice2" : " A small machine to make coffee",
			"Choice3" : "A Digital device on a chip which performs basic operations.",
			"Answer": "Choice3",
			"Explanation": "A microporcessor is a digital device on a chip which performs basic operations."
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" :13,
			"Question" : "What is a special very high-speed memory that is used to speed up and synchronizing with high-speed CPU?",
			"Answer": "Cache Memory",
			"Explanation": "Cache Memory is special very high-speed memory that is used to speed up and synchronizing with high-speed CPU."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 14,
			"Question": "What is RAM?",
			"Choice1" : "A Truck",
			"Choice2" : " A Goat",
			"Choice3" : "Memory for your computer",
			"Answer": "Choice3",
			"Explanation": "RAM is the memory for a computer. It is not refering to RAM trucks or ram goats."
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 15,
			"Question": "What is Java? (Check All that Applies)",
			"Choice1" : "Something you can buy at Starbucks",
			"Choice2" : "Something made from beans imported from Columbia",
			"Choice3" : "A OO high level general purpose programming language",
			"Answer" : [3],
			"Explanation" : "In terms of programming, Java is an OO high level general purpose programming language."
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 16,
			"Question" : "GNU stands for GNU is Not Unix.",
			"Answer" : "True",
			"Explanation" : "GNU does in fact stand for GNU is Not Unix.  So then what does GNU stand for? GNU stands for GNU is Not Unix.  But what does GNU stand for?"
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 17,
			"Question" : "Which are  computer peripherals? (Choose All that Apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Mouse",
			"Choice2" : "Flash Drive",
			"Choice3" : "An Add-on for your car",
			"Answer" : [1,2],
			"Explanation" : "An add-on for your car is not (always) a computer peripheral"
		}
	],
	"Quiz2": [
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 1,
			"Question" : "n = 5, a = 3 , sum = n + a  What is sum?",
			"Answer": "8",
			"Explanation": "Sum is n + a, which is 5 + 3 = 8."
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 2,
			"Question_1": "prod = i * j, i = ",
			"Question_2": "j = 7, print(prod) //27",
			"Answer": "3",
			"Explanation": "prod is i * j and after the code, results in 27.  if j = 7, i must equal 3."
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 3,
			"Question" : "To typecast a variable as a string in python, you need to use str(x)",
			"Answer" : "True",
			"Explanation" : "The str() function allows you to typecast variables as strings."
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 4,
			"Question": "What are possible values of a boolean variable? (Select all that apply)",
			"Choice1" : "True",
			"Choice2" : "5.6",
			"Choice3" : "False",
			"Answer" : [1,3],
			"Explanation" : "Boolean values are either true or false."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num": 5,
			"Question": "x = 10, if x > 5: print(Big Number!), else: print(Small Number!)  What is the output?",
			"Choice1" : "Big Number!",
			"Choice2" : "Small Number!",
			"Choice3" : "Null",
			"Answer": "Choice1",
			"Explanation": "x = 10, which is greater than 5, so the output would be Big Number!"
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 6,
			"Question" : "Define a variable x that equals  5.6",
			"Answer": "x = 5.6",
			"Explanation": "The answer is x = 5.6"
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 7,
			"Question" : "t = {} is the proper way to declare an array in python.",
			"Answer" : "False",
			"Explanation" : "t = [] is the proper way to declare an array in python."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num" : 8,
			"Question": "What HTML element creates an ordered list?",
			"Choice1" : "ol",
			"Choice2" : "ul",
			"Choice3" : "li",
			"Answer" : "Choice1",
			"Explanation" : "The ol element creates an ordered list."
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 9,
			"Question" : "What are multi-variable types in python?  (Select all that apply)",
			"Choice1" : "List",
			"Choice2" : "Band",
			"Choice3" : "Dictionary",
			"Answer" : [1,3],
			"Explanation" : "There is no variable type called Band in python."
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 10,
			"Question_1": "DOM stands for Document ",
			"Question_2": "Model",
			"Answer": "Object",
			"Explanation": "DOM stands for Document Object Model."
		},
		{
			"Type" : "Text",
			"Question_Num" : 11,
			"Question" : "What HTML element is used to make text bold?",
			"Answer": "<b>",
			"Explanation": "<b> is the HTML element used to make text bold."
		},
		{
			"Type": "SC",
			"Question_Num" : 12,
			"Question": "What is a Byte?",
			"Choice1" : "Ouch, you bit me!",
			"Choice2" : "Take a byte out of an apple",
			"Choice3" : "A group of binary digits or bits",
			"Answer" : "Choice3",
			"Explanation" : "A byte is a group of binary digits or bits."
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 13,
			"Question" : "Bit is the lowest storage unit.",
			"Answer" : "True",
			"Explanation" : "Bits are the lowest storage unit."
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 14,
			"Question_1": "ASCII stands for American ",
			"Question_2": "of Information Interchange",
			"Answer": "Standard",
			"Explanation": "ASCII stands for American Standard of Information Interchange."
		},
		{
			"Type": "TF",
			"Question_Num": 15,
			"Question" : "There are 7 bits in a byte",
			"Answer" : "False",
			"Explanation" : "There are 8 bits in a byte."
		},
		{
			"Type": "Blank",
			"Question_Num": 16,
			"Question_1": "In java, text can be saved as a ",
			"Question_2": "or char",
			"Answer": "String",
			"Explanation": "Text can be saved as a String or a char in java."
		},
		{
			"Type": "MC",
			"Question_Num" : 17,
			"Question" : "How good is this site?  (Select all that apply)",
			"Choice1" : "Great",
			"Choice2" : "Informative",
			"Choice3" : "Terrible",
			"Answer" : [1,2],
			"Explanation" : "You are wrong, this website is Great"
		}
	]
}